Yujian 'Charles' Tang

University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill yujian@live.unc.edu • Phone: (919) 741-4667

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My current research topic is on automating the segmentation of subcortical structures in macaque brains using deep learning on a convolutional neural network. Previous research experience includes image processing in neuroimaging, and data cleaning for mobile crowdsensing. Future research interests are in applications of deep learning in data cleaning.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill (Expected)

Chapel Hill, NC August 2015-May 2019

Miami, FL

B.S., Computer Science Minors: Statistics, Computer Science

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Neuro Image Research and Analysis Labs

Chapel Hill, NC Research Assistant August 2018-Present

Mentor: Dr. Martin Styner

Research Experience for Undergraduates, National Science Foundation

Research Intern May 2018-August 2018

Mentors: Dr. Niki Pissinou, Samia Tasnim

Neuro Image Research and Analysis Labs Chapel Hill, NC

June 2017-May 2018 Research Assistant

Mentors: Dr. Martin Styner, and Dr. Sun-Hyung Kim

WORK EXPERIENCE

Department of Computer Science, UNC Chapel Hill, NC

Undergraduate Learning Assistant (COMP 283) Fall 17, Spring 18, Fall 18

Professor: Dr. David Plaisted

ITS Franklin, UNC Chapel Hill, NC

Middleware Intern June 2017-August 2017

Department of Computer Science, UNC Chapel Hill, NC

Undergraduate Learning Assistant (COMP 410) Fall 16

Professor: Dr. David Stotts

nCino Wilmington, NC

Developer Intern June 2016-August 2016

HONORS

NC State Math Contest Scholarship Winner, 2015

Undergraduate Learning Assistant of the Year Nominee, 2018

PRESENTATIONS, PRECEDINGS, AND PAPERS

"Adapting the CIVET Pipeline for Macaque Brains", Computer Science Research Symposium, May 2018